Sam Gejdenson Papers 2001.0008
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, undated, 1966-2001
  - Submaries and Military Issues, undated, 1981-1996 (Box 40)
    - Both Iron Works, undated, 1995
    - Department of Defense Letters, undated, 1994-1996
    - Military Construction (MILCON), undated, 1987, 1989
    - Seawolf, undated, 1991-1996
    - New Attack Submarines (NAS), undated, 1994
    - Tenders at New London, undated, 1994
    - Submarines, General, undated, 1981-1991
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center (NUWC), undated, 1991-1994
    - Norfolk, undated, 1994
    - Navy New Letters, undated, 1993
    - Maritime Issues, undated, 1995-1996
    - de Tocqueville Institution, undated, 1994-1996
    - Diesel Submaries to Taiwan, undated, 1993
  - Videocassetts and Campaign files, undated, 1984-1995 (Box 41)
    - "Thunder in the Gulf" (1), undated
    - Gejdenson Fishing (1), 1984
    - Legislative Issues (4), 1988-1991
    - Television Spots (4), undated, 1991
    - Chamber of Commerce (1), undated
    - Photographs, undated
    - Campaign Material, undated
    - Gejdenson's Goals and Accomplishments, 102nd and 103rd Congresses, undated, 1991-1995
    - 1992 Campaign, undated, 1991-1993
    - 1994 Campaign Dispute, 1994 November - 1995 June
    - Franking and Donation Material, undated, 1993
    - Town Meetings, undated, 1993-1994
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1996-1999 (Box 42)
    - General Clippings, undated, 1997-1998
    - Military, undated, 1996-1998
    - Mohegans, undated, 1996-1999
    - Mashantuckets, undated, 1996-1998
    - Native American Issues, undated, 1996-1998
    - Health, undated, 1997-1998
    - Environment, undated, 1996-1998
    - Gambling, undated, 1996-1998
    - Submarine Base, undated, 1997-1998
    - Incinerator, undated, 1996
    - Poquetanuck Cove, undated, 1997
    - Electric Boat/Seawolf, undated, 1997-1998
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1990-1997 (Box 43)
    - Base Realignment, undated, 1993
    - Agriculture, undated, 1993-1995
    - Banking, undated, 1995
    - Baseball, undated, 1994-1995
    - Base Closings, undated, 1993-1994
    - Base Closure and Realignment Commission (BRAC), undated, 1995
    - Budget, undated, 1993-1995
    - Campaign Finance, undated, 1992-1994
    - Cereal, undated, 1995
    - Defense, undated, 1992-1995
    - Economy, undated, 1990-1995
    - Education, undated, 1992-1995
    - General, 1993-1995
    - Gambling, undated, 1995-1997
    - Local Politics, undated, 1995-1996
    - Mashantucket, undated, 1995
    - North American Fair Trade Agreement (NAFTA), undated, 1993
    - New London, undated, 1993-1995
    - Nuclear, undated, 1993-1995
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center/ Naval Underwater Systems Center (NUWC/NUSC), undated, 1992-1995
    - Police, undated, 1994-1995
    - Pratt & Whitney, undated, 1993-1995
    - John Rowland, undated, 1994-1995
    - Seawolf, undated, 1992-1995
  - Education, undated, 1990-2000 (Box 44)
    - President's Inauguration, undated, 1992-1993
    - Photographs, undated, 1998-2000
    - SCORE Conference Video, undated, 1998
    - After-School Care, undated, 1999-2000
    - Thompson Youth Center, undated, 2000
    - School Violence, undated, 1997-1999
    - King's Point Merchant Marines Academy, undated, 1994
    - Istook, undated, 1995
    - Libraries, undated, 1992-1998
    - National Theater for the Deaf, undated, 2000
    - Eastern Connecticut State University's Child Center, 1999-2000
    - Project Oceanology, undated, 1999-2000
    - School-to-Work Program, undated, 1994-1996
    - University of Connecticut, undated, 1990-1996, 2000
    - Special Education, undated, 1999
    - Children's Museum, undated, 2000
  - Press Releases, undated, 1985-1990 (Box 45)
    - District Events, 1985-1986
    - Voting Record, 1981-1986
    - Reelection, 1986
    - Constituent News/Mailings, 1986-1990
    - Lech Whales, 1989
    - Heritage Corridor, 1989
    - New London Day, 1985-1986
    - Town Meetings, 1987, 1989
    - Nuclear, 1988
    - Military Construction, MILCON, 1988
    - Flourescent Lights, 1988
    - Open Space, 1988
    - Iran, Attack on Roberts, 1988
    - Women, Infants, and Children (WIC), 1988
    - Environment, 1988-1989
    - Panama, 1987-1988
    - Monirealer, 1988-1989
    - DOW/WRAP (Waste Reduction Always Pays) Award, 1989
    - Oliver North, Suspended Sentence, 1989
    - Hazardous Waste Exports, 1989
    - Health, 1989
    - Foreign Relations, 1988-1989
    - Searching for Success, 1989
    - Congressional Witness Protection Act, 1989
    - Department of Defense, 1989
    - Man of the Year, 1989
    - Illegal Dumping, 1988
    - Florian Sever Act, 1988
    - Computer Workshop, 1988
    - Alcohol, 1988
    - Double Subsidy Report, 1988
    - Subcommittee, 1989
    - Budget, 1989
    - Academies, 1989
    - Recycling, 1989
    - Coast Guard Band, 1989
    - Star Wars to Drug Wars, 1989
    - Economy, 1989
    - Foley's Election, 1989
    - Electric Boat, 1988
    - Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD), 1988
    - Toy Bill, 1988
  - Journal of the House of Representatives, 1981-1996 (Box 46)
    - CDs, undated
    - 1981-1984, 1987, 1991-1996
    - 1987
    - 1991-1996
  - Foreign Trade and Exports, undated, 1988-1991 (Box 47)
    - Trade (General), undated, 1988-1990
    - New England Trade Adjustment Assistance Committee, undated, 1988-1991
    - U.S. Borders, undated, 1991
    - North American Fair Trade Agreement (NAFTA), undated, 1991
    - Shipbuilding Reform Act, undated, 1991-1992
    - Technology Preservation Act, undated, 1990-1991
    - Economic Growth Bill, undated, 1991
    - Subcommittee on International Economics, undated
    - Policy and Trade, undated, 1988-1991
    - Connecticut and Exports, undated, 1991-1992
    - Alaska n Oil, undated, 1991-1992
    - Trade Agreements, undated, 1992
    - Arab Boycotts, undated, 1991
    - Sanctions, undated, 1989-1991
    - China, undated, 1989-1992
    - Eastern Europe, undated, 1989-1992
    - Energy Bill, H.R. 776, undated
    - Europe '92, undated, 1989-1992
    - Export Enhancement Program, undated, 1991-1992
    - Exports, undated, 1988-1992
    - Foreign Availability, undated
  - Heritage Corridor, undated, 1979-1992 (Box 48)
    - Legislation, undated,1991-1992
    - Hearings, undated, 1991-1992
    - National Park Service, undated, 1988, 1990-1991
    - Technical Assistance, undated, 1990-1992
    - Press Clippingss, undated, 1989-1990
    - "Save the River,", undated, 1989-1992
    - Walking Weekend, undated, 1988-1991
    - Allies, undated, 1988-1992
    - Location, undated, 1988-1989
    - Important Resources, undated, 1988-1991
    - Historic Sites, undated, 1979-1988
    - Maps, undated, 1988
    - General files, undated, 1991-1992
  - Foreign Aid and Budget, undated, 1987-1991 (Box 49)
    - Foreign Operations Appropriations, 1989
    - Support for Eastern Europe an Democracy, 1990
    - SEED II, 1990
    - Supplemental Appropriations, 1990
    - Fiscal Year 1992, Budget, 1991
    - Budget, Fiscal Years 1990 and 1991, 1989-1990
    - Budget, Fiscal Year 1989
    - Budget Briefing Books, 1991
    - Federal Program by Function, 1989
    - Foreign Aid, 1987
    - Foreign Aid, Fiscal Years 89-91, 1988-1990
    - Foreign Aid Legislation, 1990
  - Labor Issues, undated, 1993-2000 (Box 50)
    - Jones Act, 1996
    - General files, 1994-2000
    - Outreach, 2000
    - Unions, 1998-2000
    - Privitization, 1997
    - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1999-2000
    - VARCO, 1997-1998
    - Patient/Healthcare, undated
    - Whistleblowers, 1993-1998
    - Bills, Letters, Mail, 1997-1998
    - United Technologies, Labor Grant, 2000
  - Military Issues, undated, 1979-1992 (Box 51)
    - Personel and Families, 1988-1991
    - Death Benefits, 1989-1991
    - Ex-wives, 1989
    - End Strength, 1990-1992
    - Family and Moral Welfare, and Recreation, 1990-1991
    - Retired Military Personel, 1988-1992
    - Women and Minorities, 1989-1992
    - Prisoners of War (POWs)/Missing in Action (MIAs), 1987-1991
    - Procurement, 1984-1990
    - Proliferation, 1985-1990
    - Reprograming, 1989-1990
    - SALT II, 1986
    - Sea-launch Cruise Missles, 1989-1990
    - Soldiers and Sailors, 1991
    - Soviet Threat, 1989-1990
    - STAR WARS, 1988-1992
    - Treaties and Compliance, 1979-1991
    - United Technologies Corporation, 1992
    - V-22, 1990
    - Warhead Safety, 1990
    - China/ USSR, 1989-1990
    - Germany and Eastern Europe, 1987-1990
    - USSR-Politics and Economy, 1989-1990
    - U.S./Soviet Relations, 1988-1990
    - South East Asia, 1990-1991
    - UNC, 1987-1991
    - Disarmament, 1989-1990
  - Foreign Trade and Export, undated, 1986-2000 (Box 52)
    - Asia, 1993-1997
    - Berenson/ Peru, 1997-2000
    - Cape Verde, 1996-1999
    - Becker Holocaust Case, 1997
    - Columbia, 2000
    - Daley Event, 1998
    - Dad Quig/PJ Cowan, 1999
    - District Issues, 1998-1999
    - Mohammed Essa, 1986-1989
    - Export Outreach, 1997-2000
    - Connecticut Export Firms, 1996-1999
    - Gerber, 1999-2000
    - Haiti, 1996-1998
    - Hush Kits, 1999
    - Russia, 1998
    - Children Born Abroad, 1998
    - India, 2000
    - H.R. 4095, Code of Conduct, 1997-1998
    - Iran, 1996-1998
    - Jordan, 2000
    - Ireland, 1999-2000
    - Korea, 1997-2000
    - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC), 1997
    - OP Sail/Sculpture 2000, 1998-2000
    - References, 1997-1998
    - Microenterprises, 1994-1997
    - Montigmy Clearence, 1993, 1998
    - Middle East, 1997-1998
    - H.R. 2115, 1997-1998
    - Russia n Submarines, 1999-2000
    - Foreign Policy Thank You Notes, 1997
    - Oil Spill Conference, Egypt, 1998
    - Gejdenson and Trade, 1997-2000
    - Wimpfheimer and Trade, 1997-1998
    - Gejdenson's Foreign Policy Record, 1999
    - China, 1997
  - Co-sponsored Legislation, undated, 1985-1992 (Box 53)
    - 99th Congress, undated, 1985-1987
    - 100th Congress, undated, 1987-1988
    - 101st Congress, undated, 1989-1990
    - 102nd Congress, undated, 1991-992
  - Nuclear Reglatory Comission, undated, 1981-1989 (Box 54)
    - Bogas Parts, 1987-1989
    - Fitness for Duty, undated, 1989
    - MARK I, 1987-1988
    - Containment Performance, undated, 1987
    - Design Objective, undated, 1986-1987
    - Inspector General, undated, 1981-1988
    - New York Waste Transport, 1985
    - Withdraw of Land, undated, 1987
  - Transportation, Route 11 and Route 6, undated, 1987-2000 (Box 55)
    - National Environmental Policy Act, 1987
    - Correspondence Concerning Route 11, undated, 1988-1998
    - Minutes from Route 11 Meetings, 1997-1998
    - Route 6 Reports, 1998
    - Application for Permit, 1999
    - Route 6, General, 1994-2000
    - Route 6 Breifing Documents, 1997
    - Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Route 11, 1999 February
    - Reelection Potholder, undated
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1996 (Box 56)
    - Economic Development, undated, 1992-1996
    - Education, undated, 1993-1996
    - Environment, undated, 1993-1996
    - Gateway, undated, 1993-1994
    - Health Care, undated, 1996
    - Health Care/Clinton Visit, undated, 1993-1994
    - 1996 Election, undated, 1996
    - Gejdenson's 1996 Elections, undated, 1996
    - Cereal, undated, 1996
    - Gejdenson clips, undated, 1992-1994, 1996
    - Local and National Issues, undated, 1993-1994
    - Gejdenson's 1994 Election, undated, 1994
  - Videocassettes, Undated, 1986-1992 (Box 57)
    - Unlabeled (5), undated
    - CBS News (3), 1986-1992
    - ABC News (1), undated
    - Recruitment Video (1), undated
    - China (1), 1989
    - Floor/Roudtable (4), 1992
    - Issues (14), 1992
    - Positions (7), 1991-1993
    - Gejdenson Trout Fishing (1), undated
    - Telvision Spots (2), undated
    - Education Videos on the Legislature (3), 1989
    - Gejdenson Tapes (3), undated
    - "A Blessing or a Curse?" (1), undated
    - "Stopping the Coming Ice Age" (1), undated
  - Travel for Speeches, Campaign Documents, undated, 1982-1988 (Box 58)
    - Roslyn, NY, 1986 May 4
    - Westchester, NY, 1986 April20
    - Jewish Conference, undated
    - Boston, MA, 1986 January 12
    - Queens, NY, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 January 13
    - Philidelphia, PA, 1985 Novermber 18
    - Long Beach, NY, 1985 November 10
    - Phildelphia, PA, Israeli Bonds, 1985 June 2
    - Ohio, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 September 22
    - Emanan, New York City, 1984 December 16
    - Chicago, IL, United Jewish Federation, 1985 May 29
    - Mocer-Sussex, Yam Hosha, 1985 April 2
    - Jewish Community Center, 1985 May 5
    - New York, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 June 3
    - Silver Springs, MD, Temple, 1985 April 19
    - New York, America/ Israel PAC, 1985 June 13
    - Rockland, NY, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 June 20
    - Ossining, NY, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 August 3
    - Joint Action Committe for Political Affairs, 1986 August 14
    - Larchmont, NY, 1985 October 27
    - Merrick, NY, Holocaust, 1984 August 13
    - Holocaust Rememberance, 1984 April 5
    - Riverdale, America/ Israel PAC, 1986
    - Tom Rivers, Ocean County Jewish Federation, 1984 December 8, 1985 October 27
    - Goldblatt, 1985
    - Honorarium, Expenses, 1985
    - Yom Hoshoa Commemoration, 1985 April 29
    - New York, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 December 2
    - Columbia, MD, Temple, 1985 March 15
    - Washington, Holocaust Survivors, 1985 August 25
    - Roundtable Political Action Committee, 1984 February 6
    - New York City, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 December 2
    - Boston, MA, Anti-Defamation League, 1984 May 3
    - Boston, MA, JWB, 1984 April 28
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1984 March 11
    - New York, January 21
    - Boston, MA, Coast Guard Hearings, 1984 March 2
    - New Jersey, 1984
    - Washinton, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 March 11-13
    - McClean, VA, 1984 March 25
    - Wilmington, DE, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 December 14
    - Chicago, IL, JUF, 1984 January 28
    - Philidelphia, PA, America/Israel PAC, 1984 February 5
    - Philidelphia, PA, Israeli Bonds, 1984 December 6
    - Cleveland, OH, United Jewish Appeal, 1985 February 7
    - Pittsburgh, PA, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 November 15
    - Providence, RI, Anti-Defamation League, 1984 November 30
    - Newport News, VA, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 November 11
    - Suffern, NY, 1984 June 10
    - Southern Illinois, United Jewish Appeal, 1984 May 6
    - Philidelphia, PA, Delaware Valley PAC, 1984 June 18
    - Boston, MA, American Public Works Association, 1984 June 12
    - Baltimore, MD, Israeli Bonds, 1984 October 21
    - Altaltic City and New York, 1983 November 9
    - Boston, Young Lawyers, 1983 December 5
    - Boston, MA, 1983 April
    - Chicago, IL, 1983 January 17
    - Charlotte, SC, America/Israel PAC and United Jewish Appeal, 1983 Noveember 6, 1983 August 7
    - Chicago, IL, 1983 April- June
    - Cleveland, OH, 1983 April 24
    - Erie, PA, 1983 November 20
    - Greenwich, CT, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 November 15
    - Farmington, CT, Hublein, 1983 February 14
    - Houston, TX, 1983 May 2
    - Livingston, NY, 1983 June 12
    - Long Island, 1983 June 23
    - Minneapolis, MN, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 November 7
    - Rhode Island, New England Rural Leadership, 1983 March 19
    - Memphis, TN, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 January 11
    - Milwaukee, WI, 1983 April 1
    - Monticello, NY, 1983 June 17
    - New York, NY, 1983 April 10
    - Springfeild, MA, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 October 30
    - Scarsdale, NY, 1983 June 2
    - Stamford, CT, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 November 10
    - Washington, D.C. Employment Management Association, 1983 October 13
    - Waterbury, CT, 1983 September 25
    - Westport, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 December 3
    - Wichita, KA, United Jewish Appeal, 1983 October 9
    - Press, Correspondence and Campaign Documents, 1982-1988
  - Central America, undated, 1988-1992 (Box 59)
    - University of Connecticut's Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies, Founding, 1991
    - Fiscal Year 1992, White House Budget Requests, 1991
    - Human Rights in Latin America, 1991
    - Post Cold War, undated
    - ANDEAN, 1990
    - Brazil, 1990-1991
    - Bolivia, 1990
    - Canada, Interparlimentary Group, 1988-1992
    - Caribbean, Debt for Development, 1990
    - Colombia, 1990-1992
    - Cuba, 1991-1992
    - Debt for Natural Conservation, 1988-1990
    - Enterprise for America, 1990-1992
    - El Salvador, 1989-1991
  - Education Files, undated, 1991-2000 (Box 60)
    - Abstinence Education, 1997-1999
    - Americorps, 1999-2000
    - Blue Ribbon Schools, 1992-2000
    - Character Counts, 1995-1996, 2000
    - Charter Schools, 1996-2000
    - Class Size, 1998-2000
    - Press Clippings, 1997-1999
    - School Facilities Report, undated
    - School Construction, 1997-2000
    - Education in Connecticut, 1995-1997
    - Learning Disabilies Conference, 1998
    - Reading Funding, 1999
    - Magnet Schools, 1993-1994, 1999
    - Private Schools, 2000
    - Record of Education, 1994
    - "We the People", 1997-1999
    - GOALS 2000, 1994-1997
    - Grants, 1996-2000
    - Access, 1999-2000
    - Healthy Start, 2000
    - High School, 1993
    - Hugh O'Brian Youth Leadership (HOBY), 1998, 2000
    - HOPE Scholarship, 1996-1997
    - Individuals with Disabilities Education Act, IDEA, 1997, 2000
    - Impact Aid, 1991-1994
    - Serving the Military Child Conference, 1998
    - LEARN 2000, undated
    - Library of Congress Local Legacies, 2000
    - Parent/Teacher Assoication, 1993-1994
    - School-to-Work Program, 1996-1998
  - Legislative Files, undated, 1980-1995 (Box 61)
    - General Dynamics, 1990-1995
    - MTC Visit, 1991
    - Defense-related Inititive, undated
    - Persian Gulf, 1991
    - Trident Letter, 1989
    - Simultaneous Candidacies, 1989-1990
    - Topeka (SSN 754), 1989
    - SSN 21/ Seawolf, 1989-1990
    - Stonington, 1987-1991
    - UNC/SOS, 1991
    - Question Period, 1990-1991
    - Economic Development, 1987-1991
    - Patents, 1990-1991
    - Cliff Neal, 1990-1991
    - Study Circles, 1990-1991
    - National Issue Forum, 1989-1990
    - de Vivo, 1990
    - Congressional Witness Protection Act, 1988-1990
    - Build America, 1990
    - H.R. 3428, 1987-1988
    - Van and Light Truck Safety, 1980-1988
  - Transportation and Housing, undated, 1996-2000 (Box 62)
    - Transportation and Equality Act, 1996-1999
    - HUD Middletown, 1996-1997
    - HUD Grants, 1998-2000
    - HUD Office, 1997-1999
    - HOPE VI, undated
    - Middletown Housing Authority, Long River Village, 1995-1996
    - "Find the Good and Praise It: ISTEA Success Stories", 1996-1997
    - S. 1173, 1997-1998
    - CRS: Reports for Congress, Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficancy Act (ISTEA) Reauthorization, 1997-1998
    - Committe Report: Building Efficient Surface Transportation Act, 1998 March 25
    - H.R. 2400, 1998
  - Defense, Legislative Files, undated, 1988-1993 (Box 63)
    - Economic Impact Statements, 1993
    - HUD Norwich, 1991
    - New London Housing Disposition, 1990-1991
    - Land Trust, 1989
    - FMHA Condos, 1988
    - Lead Point Grant, 1993
    - Base Closure and Realignment Commissionc (BRAC), 1991, 1993
    - Efficiency Panel, 1993
    - P-105 Site Approval, 1992-1993
    - Realignment, 1993
    - Phildelphia Law Suit, 1993
    - Gary Motin, 1991-1993
    - 688 Submarines, 1980-1992
    - Recount, 1992-1993
    - Local Base Closure Group, 1993
    - Biographies, undated
    - Cost Analysis, 1991
    - Military Construction, Fiscal Year 1993, 1991-1992
    - LABS, 1991
    - Naval Undersea Systems Center (NUSC) Letters and Meetings, 1990-1992
    - CDBG Formula, 1993
    - Base Clsosure and Realignment Commission (BRAC) Community Closures, 1993
    - Memo to Aspin, 1993 March 10
    - Closing Leak, 1993
    - Courter, 1993 February 24
    - Naval Underwater Submarine Center (NUSC) -- GAO, 1991
    - Dinner Lists, undated
    - Testimony, 1991, 1993
    - Review, 1993
    - Base Closures, 1988-1989
    - BCC, 1991
    - Community Petitions, 1993
    - Methodology, 1993
    - Hefner Letters, 1990-1991
    - Hearings, 1991 August 27
    - COBRA, 1991
    - Reports, 1991
    - Naval Undersea Systems Center (NUSC), 1991
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1996 (Box 64)
    - Amtrak, undated, 1992-1994, 1996
    - Congressional Issues, undated, 1995-1996
    - Guns/Crime, undated, 1993-1994
    - Connecticut Businesses, undated, 1996
    - Connecticut News/Businesses, undated, 1993-1994
    - Connecticut Politics, 1996
    - Federal Legislation, undated, 1996
    - Energy, undated, 1995-1996
    - Election, undated, 1996
    - Defense, undated, 1996
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center/ Electric Boat/Submarine Base, undated, 1996
    - Submarine base/ Electric Boat, undated, 1992-1994
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1995 (Box 65)
    - Taiwan, undated, 1992-1993
    - Tourism, undated, 1994-1995
    - University of Connecticut, undated, 1992-1995
    - Waste/Energy, undated, 1995
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1994-1995
    - Taxes, undated, 1992-1995
    - Transportation, undated, 1992-1995
    - Veterans, undated, 1992-1995
    - Editorial Board, undated, 1993
    - Gejdenson Clips, undated, 1993-1994
    - Election, undated, 1994
  - Admistrative Records, 1985-1992 (Box 66)
    - Legislative Activity Guides, 99th Congress, 102nd Congress, 1st session, 1985-1986, 1991
    - Co-sponsored Legislation, 1988-1990
    - Dear Collegue Letters, 1992-1994
    - Co-sponsored Health Bills, 1988-1992
    - Robo Letters, 1987-1990
  - Health and Homelessness, undated, 1987-1997 (Box 67)
    - Food Allergy Initiative, 1996-1997
    - Paul Healey Case, 1995-1997
    - For Profit Hospice Hearing, 1997 March 7
    - Kassenbaum-Kennedy Bill, 1995-1997
    - Project Link, 1991-1992
    - Connecticut Statistics, 1997
    - Vernon Housing, 1992-1993
    - Park West Residents, 1995-1996
    - Pfizer, 1993-1994
    - Medicare, 1993-1997
    - Jack Nuttal, undated
    - Medicare Mailing Sheets, 1992-1994
    - Medicare Managed Care, 1995-1996
    - Breast Cancer, 1991-1997
    - AIDS, 1989-1996
    - Children's Health Insurance, 1997
    - Diabetes, 1994-1996
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994
    - Lyme Disease, 1988-1997
    - Rockville Community Health Center, 1995-1996
    - Tourette Syndrome, 1995-1996
    - Shelter and Care, 1992
    - Waterbury, 1991-1992
    - New London Housing Authority, 1996
    - Housing Act, 1997
    - Medicare, Local Clippings, 1995
    - Medicare Fraud, 1995-1996
    - Graduate Studies, Medicine, 1995
    - Workers' Commission, 1996-1997
    - Mystic Aquarium, 1995-1997
    - The Blind, 1993-1995
    - Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), 1995
    - Ackerman Unblind Bill, 1994-1995
    - Consolidated Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act,COBRA, 1987-1995
    - Dexfenfluramine, 1995-1997
  - Press Releases, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 68)
    - PAC Contributions, 1985-1986
    - Letters to the Editor, 1985-1986
    - Local Races, undated, 1985-1986
    - Debates, undated, 1986
    - State Legislature, undated, 1985
    - Other Connecticut Races, undated, 1985-1986
    - Republican Attacks, undated, 1985-1986
    - Gejdenson's Record, undated, 1986-1987
    - Advance Light Truck Bill, 1987 February 19
    - Appliance Efficancy, 1987 March 4
    - New G.I. Bill, 1987 March 17
    - Volunteer Awards, 1987 March 27
    - Academy Nominations, 1987 April 11
    - Foreign Aid Amendement, 1987 April 1
    - Gejdenson Joins Long Island Sound Caucus, 1987 April 23
    - Roberts Resign, 1987 April 30
    - Committee O.K.s Groundwater, 1987 May 6
    - Budget Statement, 1987 January 5
    - Gejdenson Meets with Dairy Farmers, 1987 January 7
    - Groundwater, 1987 January 27-28
    - O'Neil/Benga, 1986
    - Statewide Republicans, undated, 1986
    - Moffett-O'Neil, undated, 1986
    - Senator Dodd, undated, 1985-1986